amplifr.com 2017-06-06

# Use of Contact Information

Amplifr provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the
collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this
website, located at https://amplifr.com ("Site" ).
By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this
Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or
using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing,
deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the
United Kingdom. If you reside outside the UK your personally identifiable information will be
transferred to the UK, and processed and stored there under UK privacy standards.
By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and
processing in the UK.
Information Collection and Use
Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the
product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service,
to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.
Information Collected Upon Registration
If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to
become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to Amplifr.
This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you
desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we
may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email
address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us
with.
Use of Contact Information
In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with
information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you
decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from
us, please un­follow us, or follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the
communications.

Log Data
When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends
whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). This Log Data may include information such as your
IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web­pages you visit, the
search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing
the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log
on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s
technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally
identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of
Service.
Cookies
Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data
and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your
computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information.
Amplifr may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you
interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic
routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain
features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect
from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be
used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by
following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept
cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to
prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Service Providers
We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us,
including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, billing, customer relationship, database
storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally
identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these

functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations
requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement
Amplifr cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce
and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law
enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or
appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property
and rights of Amplifr or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop
any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.
Business Transfers
Amplifr may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally
identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets
or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the
new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this
Privacy Policy.
Changing or Deleting Information
If you are a registered user of the Site, you may access and update or correct the information
you provided to us by e­mailing us at help@Amplifrapp.com.
Security
Amplifr is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable
information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect
your information from unauthorized access. We will make any legally­required disclosures of
any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored
personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time
possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law
enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore
the reasonable integrity of the data system.

Links to Other Websites
Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an
endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not
exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or
other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you.
Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable
information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of
the other websites you visit.
Our Policy Towards Children
The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or
her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she
should contact us at help@Amplifrapp.com. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable
information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us
with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.
Changes to this Policy
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to
information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our
Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this
Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 20 2016.
If you have any thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy please let us know.
